Hello guys, welcome to my channel.  This is going to be the
first video of our channel.  Today we
will learn how to fill the claim form of ICIC Lambor.   There are
two types of ICC Lambd claim forms.  There is one
motor insurance and one
health insurance.  Today I
will teach you how to fill the motor insurance claim form.   The
insurance claim form will be the
same for two-wheelers and four-wheelers.
Be it a truck, a bus or a car
, it remains exactly similar.  There is
no change in this.  And I will tell you point to
point how to fill it
and where not to make a mistake
because I have been doing this claim
work for about four
to five years and I have
worked in many companies and this is the first video of my channel
and this is my motive
because when many people come to take a claim.
When his car met with an accident,
many people came to claim.  Like this
car.  Many people's car gets hit
or damaged by something, so
when people come to make a claim,
they do not know
how to fill the claim form, what
documents will be required, how will the process be,
so I will tell you everything from A to Z,
what all you have to do, how to
fill the claim form and to whom to submit it,
what is the process, I will
clear all your doubts in today's video,
if you have any doubt then you
can comment,
I will tell you in the comment.  So this is our first
video.  So first of all you have to come here.  First of all,
I will give you the link of this claim form in the description.
You have to download it from there.
But this is only for those people
who have an ICICI policy.  There are types in policies also.  I will
also tell you which
type each is.  Like what is a first party
?  What is a third party?
What is cash to cash?  What
is a bumper?  What is normal?  What
is 50-50?  In this way there are many types of policies.
Which category of policy is it?  By doing this
I will tell you everything in one video.
So stay tuned and don't skip even a single part.
And as I said,
you must be seeing the claim form.  First came
information about insurance.  So let me
tell you first of all.  Like we have
two persons.  First of all we will take two
persons.  One became Rahul
and the other became Mukesh.
Mukesh is Rahul's friend.
This is Mukesh.  Mukesh is the owner in whose name
this car is.
This is the owner.  And Rahul has
asked Mukesh to drive the car.  Like Rahul
took the car from his friend Mukesh and
it met with an accident somewhere.  Like he is
driving this car, so his car has been hit somewhere.
So now we will see how this claim form will be filled.
If Mukesh is the owner then
if Mukesh has made it a hit then I will
tell you that also.  If any other person has hit it, I will
tell you that too.  Like we will take you now
Rahul.  Like Rahul has hit.
So I will tell you everything that will happen during Rahul's time and
what documents will be required for Rahul.
So, first of all, it will come to you
and when you have to go to collect this claim,
both the persons will have to go at that time.  The person who was
driving the car, like Rahul
was driving and Mukesh who is the owner, both of them should go.
So but the main is definitely of honor.  If he
denies that he will not go or
whatever or if there is even a little damage to it, then
if he is not able to come in any situation,
but it is compulsory for the owner to go or it is
compulsory to fill the claim form and give it to the owner
because the owner's signature is required, so
how will he sign if someone does
not have a PAN card, then how will he
fill the claim form because there are a lot of doubts that right now,
four documents are required in
which one is a PAN card, so
if someone does not have a PAN card, then how will he
fill the claim form, will he
not get the claim, I will clear all his doubts right now, let
us assume
that Rahul is the owner and Rahul has taken his car
and first of all he came to us
here, you will see that first of all you have to keep in
mind that this motor insurance should be clean
form, if you have ICICI
Lambar insurance then you will need this
clean form, whether it is a two wheeler or a
four wheeler, if there is any other
insurance, they will tell you about your insurance
policy.  The name
of the insurance company will be on it and
you will get to know about your insurance policy.
So you just comment to me and I will
fill that claim form also.  And first of all,
as it comes here, the policy or cover note cover
note number will be available to you on your insurance policy.
You will get this number only on the insurance policy.
Because when you are
transferring from ICICI, like last time you were in New India, then
its policy number must have changed,
this policy number changes every time, that means
if you are running in the same company then it will remain the same,
if you have changed the company
then the policy number would have changed, so first of all
you will
see the policy number, your insurance policy which is
lying with you, there will be a policy
number, you will see it there,
first of all it will be like this, I am
taking 35 example, 35 8 7 9 2
1 0, then there will be brackets, then 0 0, then there will be brackets,
then 0, like this there will be a claim form
number, whatever it is, you have to write it,
then after that the claim number will come,
keep this in mind, you will get it at the very last.
Of course it is written first but
it will be found last.
You won't get this first.  This
is available at the end because you will get it as soon as you register.
And there are
two ways for you to register.  One thing is that
this website is from their website that after going to a website of ICICI LB.
You have to register your claim from here or
register it on their toll free number.
So if you don't even like you don't want to do it yourself.
So I will also
tell you the method of how it will be done.  So
after that came the name.  Right now many
people are confused as to whose name is here.
As we can see, the
information about insurance is about the
insured.  All these details will be there, yes,
like this owner is our Mukesh in this.
Like our owner of this car is
Mukesh.  So all the details in this will be filled in of Mukesh
only.  If you are unable to find out in
whose name the vehicle is registered because there are many
doubts, then you must have received a registration
certificate which we call RC.
There you would have either found a page
or a small card type.
Meaning you must know the RC.  Meaning RC
is received.  When you buy a car, you
get some documents along with it.
You will see the name there.  So his
name will be written there.  Like right now we believe that
Mukesh's name is written.  Here we will
write Mukesh.   Will
fill Mukesh's details.
True Mukesh, whatever space one bracket is left,
like we assume Kumar or anything.
His surname will be K M A R, this means
Mukesh Kumar.  Like his name would be.  You just
fill it in the same way as you need to fill the address, for
address you need Aadhar card.
Who needs an Aadhaar card?  Mukesh's.  And the
documents that I am telling you about,
you need Aadhar Card.  If
you turn behind it, you will see Mukesh's address.
So you have to fill it completely.   It can also happen like this, if
we assume that it is Delhi,
Delhi, Delhi,
Delhi, X and
Z places, whatever it is, you have to write the ward number,
house number,
flat number, whatever it is, you have to
write it similar to that and after that write its PIN
number, let's say 79
2, it will be
its PAN number, here the PAN number
and this mobile number are most important.
In this you have to enter Mukesh's mobile number
and where will you see Mukesh's mobile number.
You have to open the
insurance page again
when you got insured. Many
people do not know which
company's insurance they have, so you have to
call the person from whom you got the insurance and tell him to
send me the insurance policy. There will be a number on the policy, the
last four to five digits on it.
Many have complete numbers and many have four
digits, so whoever has that number,
like many times it happens, like there is a
car in Mukesh's name, Mukesh's cousin has
registered his number,
so you have to tell him also that brother, I am
taking a claim, then you will get a call and this is the
most important,
this process of mobile number is the most important, so for
now we assume that this is Mukesh
's number, Mukesh has entered his number,
that too by checking the policy number, the
number is written on the policy where the policy is.
We have written down its policy number,
whatever that policy number may be.  Then
after that enter the mail here, like his
mail would be Mukesh@gmail.com,
you just have to write it in the boxes.  I'm
writing it out.  You have to write in the boxes.
Write carefully.
Then after that you have to see the
customer occupation asked here,
what does that customer do?
Now, if someone is from IIT and
is in IIT Professional then you have to tick here.
If he is in Defence or Ministry then
tick here or he works for Government or
Administration or he is a
corporate employee, then if he is not any of these then
tick on Other and
write that here, like we
can write something about him here,
like he is the owner.
Meaning he is the owner, means he will be the owner of some place,
whatever it is, you write it here as to what he owns,
so this is the PAN number, if you
want a PAN card then there will be a number on the PAN card,
you have to register it here,
write it here, the PAN card number will be like this, whatever the
PAN card number is, you have to write it
in the box here, after that you need Aadhar,
write the Aadhar number here, exactly as
I am telling, all this will
appear to be of Mukesh only.  This
PAN number will also be of Mukesh.  Aadhar will also be
of Mukesh.  For now, all the
documents I have mentioned will appear to be of Mukesh.  There is
nothing in this about what Rahul was running.  Right now only Mukesh's will be installed.
This number is C KYC, its customer
KYC, let it remain.  After that this also has to be left.  Let
the nature of the relationship and
these two parts remain.  You have to come after that.
Information about vehicle: For this you will
need RC which is the registration certificate, to
fill this you must have it
in your phone
or in your hand and
you must need it.  First of all the
registration number is asked.  This will be the registration number.
Like his vehicle number which is the
car number or scooter number,
we can write DLL
5 8 7
whatever it is by doing DL BM, whatever his
vehicle number will be and the chassis number will come here, if
you open the RC then the chassis number will be visible in the RC, so
if it is not visible in the RC, if
you do not find it then you have to open your vehicle.  The
driver seat there is
below the driver seat.  Or you have to
write it from there.
So either you have to write from RC.  And if it
is a scooter, then there is a box like structure in the front of the scooter where the
legs are kept.
It becomes open.  If it
is a new scooter, if it is old, it is of an old model.
So for that you will have to lay that scooter on the right side.
So it is on the right side of its
right side where the slip is,
look there they will tell you where it
comes.  But maximum you can
write down the chase number from the RC itself.  There will be a chess
number there, something like MEL 4JK
876.  You have to
write that.
After that came the
details about the driver at the time of the
accident.  This is what you have to keep in mind here.  This
is the detail about the driver.  This is the most important
and the most crucial.  If this is true then do
not skip it even by 1%.  Because if
any mistake happens in this then your car will become
no claim.  No claim means
you will not get any claim.  So first of all
you need a driving license which we
call DL.  Driving license.
Who wants that?  We want that from Rahul.
We need Rahul who was driving the car at
that time and in that also we have to see two-three things.
Like we won't find Mukesh here.
If by chance Mukesh, who is the owner, is
driving the car, then
Mukesh's license should have been issued here, then Mukesh
's license will be issued.  But if Mukesh, for now let
us assume that Mukesh was
not driving the car and Rahul was driving, then the
DL will also be in Rahul's name.  So
before filling all this in the driving license, first of all you have to
look at the driving license and first of all
you have to see what features are
written in it.  First you will see his
name.  You have to check the name, it is the
same name.  Then father name
father, father name has to be checked on his DL.   It
is the same, there is no change.  Then after that the
DL
number will be
of 15 digits
or it can be more than that.  So you have to
write the DL number.
After that the main thing you have to check is if
he is driving a four wheeler, if he is driving a
two wheeler like he is driving a motor
scooter, for that he needs a
motorcycle
without gear, he needs a license,
if he is driving a bike then he needs a
motorcycle
with gear,
if he is driving a car which is a family vehicle then
he needs LM V lower motor
vehicle, if he is driving a bigger vehicle like a bus, if he is
driving a truck then he needs a heavy motor
vehicle, if he is driving a truck then
he needs a truck or a four wheeler which is
for transport, then it is a
heavy motor vehicle, if he is
driving a family vehicle like we drive for the family
and it is a personal vehicle then it is a
lower motor vehicle, if he is
driving a motorcycle etc. then if he is driving a scooter then it is a
motorcycle with gear, but it is
very important to check this.  If he is
driving a four wheeler then he does
not even have LM.  If the remaining three are there then this vehicle will
still be no claim.  There will be
no claim from heavy motor vehicle also because
he is driving a personal vehicle and the
authority of personal vehicle has not approved
that if you have a personal vehicle then
you can drive a heavy motor vehicle, so nowadays
heavy motor vehicle is made separately, LMB is made
separately, motorcycle with gear is
made separately, so if many people have
three or four licenses on a single license, then it is
well and good that yes,
these four are there, meaning whatever the person is
driving, it is compulsory to have that thing.   The
car will not run without it.  Without that the
claim will not be received.  You have to check this.
If he is using LMB then it is fine.
So if it has LMB written on it then there is
no problem.  Then he has to come here, so
you have to come here and
fill the details here.  Like first of all his name has to be
filled.  Rahul's name will come here.   It could be
Rahul Gupta.
Like if it is Rahul Gupta then the name of Mukesh Kumar,
who is the owner, will not appear.  Here the
name of the person for whom you are applying for the license will
appear.  And here you have to write the license number.  For
example, whatever the number may be, DL
98 7, whatever it may be, you have to fill
its number in the boxes.  So you have to tick here
because if the owner is running it here then the
owner's tick will be put here.  If the owner
is not there, like if we assume that the
owner was not driving the vehicle, then it will be written as 'other than',
meaning someone other than the owner was driving, some
different vehicle, and here the details of the
accident have to be filled carefully and
its photo also has to be taken. When you have to fill it,
then its photo has to be taken, like
what is the date of your vehicle today, like today is 10th
September, so your vehicle met with an accident on 5th September,
here we have to write 59
2025 25 and at what time it happened because
very rare are the people
who will remember the exact time that yes, it was happening at the exact time, so
like right now, if you assume that it happened at
4:50, it happened at 4:50, if
you do not remember then you can write 5:00,
but try to enter the exact time
and do not change the time too much,
like if it happened in the evening then write 'evening' and
fill it very carefully and you
must take its photo so that you do not forget when you get a call.
It is written exact
location of accident.
Address the spot of accident with landmark.
Many times it happens that if an
accident has just happened, it
depends on where it happened.  If
many people's vehicles have met with an accident, then it is not possible that
you may not know
where it happened.  You have to ask this from someone nearby.
If you are unable to find it then
ask nearby whether there is any shop or
any place nearby.  Like we write, there will be an
accident on Delhi Highway, Delhi Delhi Delhi Highway, Delhi Highway.  Here
you should tell the address where it happened.
And after this, when you have to fill this, you have to tell the Give Brief
Disc Description of the Accident,
how the car crashed.  So first of all
you have to look at the car.  Now I have
posted a photo
of this car.  You can see that there is complete
overall damage here.  It happened on this side.
As you can see, the
maximum damage has occurred on this side.   The
rest of the car is clean.  So you have to take a claim.
So you have to see that maximum
customers know how the
car has become a hit.  So you can tell how it became a hit.
If you are not able to understand then you have to see
how the car got hit.  So what
could be the reason for this?  Now let us say that it is
with someone.  It does
n't look like that at all.  It is important to look carefully and
write very carefully what we are writing.
Now as we can see here,
it must have rung with some vehicle.
Here it must have been with the truck because the
back side of the truck is a little like this.  By doing this it gets
raised.  This
is the back side of the truck.  But this back side hit, this
side of the truck must have been hit.  If the truck is on that
side then it will be on
this side of the truck.  There must have been a hit here
which we can see because
now we have enough time to
see and tell which customer is
telling the truth and who is lying.  And we
can also tell by looking when the train has rung
and when it has not rung.  We have been here for so long.  Right now, like
here, either it has
collided with the truck because it is damaged from below or
this car.  If you can see, there
is damage here also.  The tyre
is perfect and the rim is also perfect.   There is
no special impact here.
So you can see that yes, I have
so much knowledge about the vehicles that I can understand
how the vehicle might have hit.
We can tell by looking.  So this is not much more.
We can write
here as hit by truck hit by unknown
vehicle because if we
give a very long description then it will be a
problem for us because when we
get a call then we can tell in it what
happened step by step
but for now it is not necessary to write so long
and the longer we write the more it will be a
problem for us and if there is a mismatch then the
vehicle goes into no claim, there
should not be a mismatch as we can see that
one bumper of this vehicle is broken.   First of all the
bumper is broken.  The headlight is broken.
This fender is broken.
This is the left side front window
which we can see.  Which is roughly what we can
see.  This mirror will go away.  We will
replace its mirror and say that yes, this mirror is broken, this one, the
main things which are broken which
we can see from outside that it is broken
because this bumper will also be replaced with a new one, this
cannot be repaired, maximum
100% of the plastic thing gets changed, it
cannot be repaired, if it is just a little
minor then no, if it is not found in the claim then
in that condition we repair something.
Otherwise we do not
repair anything.  So,
we repair the metal parts.  If you
want bumper to bumper ball then you should be careful
that you don't get everything.  You should
try not to get everything.
I will
also tell you the amount you will have to pay in that, how much amount you have to pay
to the company and how much you will get through the company.  The
video will be a bit long
but you will get A to Z details on
how to write.  So
like we can write
hit
hit by
we can write here hit by truck so we will
write truck.  If an FIR has been lodged then
we will have to write it.
If an FIR has been filed against us or he has filed it against us
or we have filed it against him, then we will have to write it
because we will have the releasing and
everything, then here we will have to
write the vehicle that was hit by truck, four wheeler,
whatever the truck may be, the name of the truck
and the number will have to be written, so like many
times there is a case of hit and run, after
hitting the truck driver or the car driver or anyone runs away, then
we will write there
hit by unknown
vehicle
is fine or unknown truck, but it will be
better if you write vehicle because when you get a
call, then at that time you can tell
which truck it was and how it was hit, so for
now you have to write only these things and
take its photo.  This is to take a photo of this whole thing.  From
here till here and the
most important thing is this date, time, place and
you will get a call on this and the call will come on the number
which you have entered here, you have written it here
and which is on your policy, the
number which you have given, you will get a call on this number
and you will be asked how this happened
and if this mismatch happens then your vehicle will become
no claim, you have to keep this in mind.
If it is someone else's number, like
a cousin's number, who had gone to get insurance, then
he entered his number.
So he also has to be told that such and such thing has happened.
So whenever the call comes, you have to
tell him that the accident happened on the 5th.   The
accident happened on 5th September.  At
5:00 pm in the evening on Delhi Highway and an unknown vehicle
hit me from the left side.
Whatever you have to write on the left hand side front,
you have to write it exactly. You have to give the exact description
if no FIR has been lodged, if an FIR has been lodged then
I will tell you that too. If an FIR has been lodged
then you have to
give the complete description and
attach a copy of the FIR along with
a releasing order. You will
see it from here. Then you have to
write the time exactly the same, the date also the same as it
will be on the FIR and the place also has to be
written from where the vehicle was picked up.   You will have to
write the place from where the police seized your vehicle.  After that your third party will come.
This is a doubt of many people.
What is this third party?  And
what will happen to those who have only third party insurance?  Because this
third party, those who have taken third party
insurance, first of all they should
go and convert it from third party to first party
because
if your car is on third party, like this car is of Mukesh,
like this car is of Mukesh, if he has it,
we take it only to the third party,
third third third third
party,
if his car hits.  Like Mukesh
's car is just its policy.
If a third party hits his car and he is
driving it as per his wish, there is
no problem with that.  Like Rahul is driving.   For
now, let's move this to a separate page.
Like we bring it here.
Mukesh is here.
Mukesh was driving the car.  Its policy is
third party.
Who did the third party and Mukesh hit?  In the evening.
In this, the insurance claim that will be received from the third
party will be received by Mukesh in the evening,
neither his car will be repaired nor
if he is injured, he will
not get anything, he will not get even 1% claim, the
meaning of third party is that we, the third
party, means for the third person, will be the first
party, that is, you will be the second party of your car, the
third will be the other person or his car.
Only he will get this.  You will
not get anything.  So, as far as I have seen till now, third party maximum
people do not use third party in their lives.
I have never seen
anyone using a third party here.  This has become a third party.
So there are many conditions in this.  Like
someone's car gets stolen.  I will
make a separate video for that.  What does it take for that
?
I will also tell you what kind of documents are required.  Now that
it has become a third party,
you should never keep it as a third party.
You always have to go to the first party.   There is a
type in the first party also.  Like it happened
in the first party.  One becomes a
bumper.
Bumper to bumper.
Then one becomes normal.
One becomes 50 50
becomes 50.  It happens bumper to bumper.
This is yours, if you have a scooter then
you will get this for 3 years.  If you have a two wheeler, it will be
yours for 3 years.  Meaning, it will have to be
renewed every year but it happens only for
3 years bumper to bumper.  If there
is a car then it will be valid for 5 years.  If there is a truck,
something else goes.  So there are different such
criteria, that is, for the four wheeler
which is LMB, it is valid for 5 years
only and for this it is valid for 3 years.
So when you look at this car after 5 years,
your 50% deduction would have been done.
If your car is 5 years old, when you bought it new, then
your car was worth Rs 10 lakh.   For example, if
your car was worth Rs
10 lakh, then after 5 years, when your 5
years are completed, by then the remaining
value of your car would be Rs 5 lakh and would have
come down to exactly 50%. At that time, you can either get a
normal policy. I will
also tell you about this, if your
policy has come down to exactly 50% or less than that, then
how do you want to increase it?
I will also tell you what to do. So, it has become
normal, like your one second,
this has become normal.
Your policy has become normal.  Like it happens normally,
like if the
company pays 40% then you will pay 60%.  In case of any
accident, like insurance of Rs. 10,000, the
company makes a bill of Rs. 10,000, for example, if it is Rs. 10,000, then the
company will pay Rs. 4,000 and
you will pay Rs. 6,000.  There are different types of this also.  Just assume that I am
talking about the normal one.  This
is your normal policy.  So in normal policy there is
40 60, there is also 30 70
, there is also 2080, there is also 1090.
No one gets 1090 done.  Absolutely, if
he gets it done by a good third party,
what will you get out of it.  So even in 2080 you have to
avoid the normal.  You have to try
that there should not be even a normal policy.  If after 5 years,
in a normal policy, the
company tells you that it will pay 70% and
you have to pay 30%.  Then you get it done.
So, the policy is made after looking at the different criteria conditions of different vehicles.
So according to this,
if it gives more than 50 if the car is in
normal condition then you should get it made normal.
Otherwise you should get a 50-50 policy.
Now, as you know,
50-50 means that the company will pay 50%.
Like there is a bill of Rs 10,000.
So the company will pay Rs 5000.  You
will pay Rs 5000.  This is your normal policy.  This is
your 50-50 policy.  So
you have to try your maximum to keep it bumper to bumper.
After that, according to the condition,
you have to keep it either normal
or according to 50-50 condition.
After that you have to come here to the third
party.
For third party, you first
need an FIR.  Without FIR,
you cannot make a third party claim.
So, in maximum chances of third party claiming against you,
everyone has put forward their claim.
Every registered person has got his vehicle
insured.  So, there is
no need for a third party.  So
try to file an FIR as well, if there are maximum chances that it does not happen then it is
well and good.  If someone
gives the settlement amount then you
can give it to him.  So the maximum you can do is
give it to him or
take it from him and leave the car at the same time.  Leave that too.  You can
leave yours too.   Get it
released, if still the customer does not
agree then an FIR will be lodged, after that the
vehicle will remain there for a long time, it will remain there for a
month at least, if
not for 10-20 days, it will remain there
in the police station, after that you will get it released
from the court, then it is a very lengthy process, so
if you do not want to take a third party then
you can cross this like this
or leave it blank, if you want to
take a third party then first of all the
insured person name, injured person name
whose name will be there, for example, let us assume Sham, SHAAN
Sham's name will come, Sham's
address will come, you will get Sham's address
from the Aadhar card only, whatever the address will be,
you have to fulfill it by doing X and Z CT and you have to
put the FIR here, without FIR
you cannot find the third party, so
if your third party vehicle is damaged
then also it will be mentioned in the FIR.  Even if a
person is harmed, it will be mentioned in the FIR.
So whatever it is, if his vehicle is
damaged, then while getting it registered, you have to get
a printout of it and attach his photo etc. along with it.  So if any
person has been injured, then whatever
bill you have, whatever medical bill of the doctor for the injury, you have to
attach it with it.
So in maximum chances, third party
people skip it.  After that the
sign came here.
Signs will appear here.
Mukesh, the owner, will sign here.  And how will you come?  Like on
PAN card.  If they are like this then they will
come like this only.  If there are some other different types then
you have to enter different types and dates, like the
date on which you have to leave the vehicle, for example, you have come to leave the vehicle on
10th at the company on 10th
2025, you have to write here that you
left the vehicle on such and such date,
after this it came here, this
came after this, this
part D of yours,
this little, for this
you will have to understand
when you have to fill it.
You also need two criteria to fill this.
As you
can see, this is a very long and lengthy process.
In this you have to check whether one
is
cashless.  There is a cashless policy and there is a
non-
cashless policy
and what is the difference between cashless and non-cashless,
this is cashless in
which you have got a bumper to
bumper policy done and from where will it be cashless, it will be
cashless from that company
from which you have bought a car from Honda, if
you have bought a car from Honda then
only Honda will insure you.  There is
a person from inside Honda company who only
does insurance.  If you have done it through him then you will get it
cashless.  Then there is
no problem because there is a
tie up with that company.  The meaning of tie up is
that we have talked to that company or any other
insurance company that
whatever claims you have, we will pay them
cashless and later, like you have
talked to ICICI or Honda that whatever
claims you have, we will
pay you.  We will not do this to the customer.
We will do it for you.  Or they have a chance to do it to their
customers as well as to
you.  But now the benefit of cashless is
that the customer does
not have to pay.  He has a liability.  There is
a delivery order.  It is a small
amount.  He has to pay that.
That has to be done on bumper to bumper policies by
paying different amounts on each policy.  So, like right
now I am telling you bumper to bumper that if you want to
buy cashless then how will you
get it cashless?  You have to first go to Honda company
and find out from them.  First of all
you have to remember who got it done from.
If your insurance is from within the company, like from
Honda, from Hondai,
if your car is insured by the same company,
then you will
not have any problem.  Then you have to
go straight.  You have to tell them that
sir, they will give me cash only in cashless mode.  So
what is the benefit of cashless?  For example,
your bill is for ₹10,000.   A
bill of ₹10,000 has been made.  So I have a lot of them,
one comes as soon as your car
is completely ready.  I
will also tell you a process of how the vehicle
is prepared and what happens.
I will tell you each and every point in the next video.  This
is the first video of our channel.  You have to
subscribe to this channel and also like it so that
I can tell you further
how to get the claim for your vehicle.
How does your car work?  How everything happens
and which policy should be taken and which should
not be taken.  I will tell you everything.
Like you have ₹10,000 bumper to bumper.
Like this bumper to
bumper
bill of ₹10,000 which has been made for you.  Your policy was bumper to
bumper and you have a bill of ₹10,000.  So
whatever amount you have to pay, you have to pay it at the maximum.
It is not that it becomes
absolutely zero.  I have
seen this many times 200 times.  I've seen 50 as well.  That
if someone has suffered a loss of Rs
2000 then what will he
pay.  But the company takes that too.  It
may charge ₹100 or ₹200 but it will take
you from ₹200 to ₹2000.
When will it go?  It can also be within Rs 2000.
When you have a bumper to bumper policy.
And in maximum chances,
you also have to keep in mind that whatever the company has
given, you also have to ask them that
you have to enter only what the company has given.
Now if you have got some work done on your own.
Like your damage was from the left side.  Let
me show you.  Like your
car was damaged on the left side.  It came
to the left side.  So if you have got something done from the right side
or something done from the back side
or something done on this window, then
you will have to make the payment for it.  That
company will not pay.  So this is your
bumper to bumper cashless pay.  What happens to non-cashless
?  Like now I started telling you
what is the non-cashless system?
Non-cashless pay is that you will have to pay
this amount, let me tell you a second ago.
How will you know in 2000
how yours came?  First of all you will get the bill from the company.
You will get the bill at the place where you got the vehicle prepared.
And after the bill, he must have received a mail.   A
mail must have come to which he must have said DO.   If
DO is meant then they might be saying delivery order or liability
or payment
or something like this, you have to
take mail from them, like your bill is made for ₹10,
then you have to subtract 10,000, on their
mail they must have told them that the company will pay you
8500,
so your remaining 1500,
this 1500 is your delivery
order, this DO is yours, which you have to
pay from your pocket, the company is paying the remaining ₹8500, that
means I am taking an exact amount
that we got work done for ₹10,
different vehicles have
different work, some have ₹100, some have
₹15000, some have ₹000,
some have ₹00,
as the amount is different on different vehicles, the
delivery order changes accordingly.
But this is what remains in bumper to bumper.  It remains
between 2000 to 200 to 2000.  So
if you have not got any other work done, you have to make this
payment to them and take the car.
This is your cashless experience.  And
what happens in non-cashless?  For example, you have
bought a car from
Honda but you have not got your insurance done from
ICICI
but from the company,
you have got it done from some other person
or from some company or from some shop, then at
this time if your bill is made for ₹100,
for example, you have got a bill of ₹100, then
you will have to pay the
entire exact amount of the bill which is made for ₹1,000.
If you want to take the car at the same time, they will not get any mail in that.
They will not receive any mail, nor will they
receive any delivery order, nor will they receive anything.
So if they want to take ₹10,000 from you, then you will
pay ₹10,000 and
you will say that I paid ₹10,000.
What benefit did I get from getting insurance
?  This is the ₹10,000 you have paid.  Its
like the company will tell you that the company will pay you ₹8,500.
So this ₹8500 will come into your bank
account.
If your bank account is cashless or non-
cashless, then you have to attach a photostat copy of the front photo of your bank account
in which you want to receive the payment.
You will get this in the bank that
1500 will be your delivery order
which will be paid to you, which no one will return,
after that the company will give you ₹8500,
if the company is genuine, then many times it
takes time, like it may take
10 to
15 days.  10 to 15 days, it
depends on your surveyor, how quickly he is a
surveyor.  There are a lot of
people involved in getting a claim for a vehicle.
As if there was an owner.
Then after that he became an advisor, a
surveyor, then a company.  In this way,
many four to five types of people are included.
We treat the company as a person.
So we will identify them as a person only.
So as we said, the
money will come into your account within 10 to 15 days.
If it is non-cashless then you have to fill this Part B
form which I had skipped for you.
Like you have to fill this Part B.
So if you have UPI, if
you can take it in UPI then you have to tick and
fill the UPI ID here.
If you do not have UPI
then you have to put a cross here and tick it
and leave the UPI ID.  Here, first of all you have to
try not to enter the details of Mukesh's account, for example, if the car belongs to Mukesh, then
you have to fill in the details of Mukesh's account only,
because
if you include too many people,
like Mukesh enters his cousin's or father's
name, bank number or account number,
it will cause more problems.  Then it becomes a very lengthy
process.  They investigate
whether this person is genuine or not and whether
this is a fraud or not.  By doing this a
very long process takes place.  Then
instead of 15 to 20 days, instead of 10 to 15 days,
they can deliver in 10 to 30 days, even 40 days.
Therefore, you have to fill Mukesh's name here only.
Mukesh's PAN copy has to be taken.
Mukesh, if this
is not cashless, if this is non-cash, if it is cashless, then
you have to skip all this.  So
you don't need to fill it.  So this company will
pay for itself.  Then your
account number will be there.
You have to fill in whatever account number is there.
So if the account is savings then it is
savings.  If there is current then there is current, if there is ginger then
ginger has to be filled in whatever it is.  So, you have to become the name of
the bank.  Like the name of the bank SB,
whatever it is yours, then it will be the name of the branch
like Delhi
Delhi, after that you have to fill the
address of the bank, you have to search on Google here,
you will get the address of the bank,
whatever it is, you have to fill it here and
IFC code
and PAN number,
you have to enter the PAN number, the
PAN number which will be there on your PAN card, you have to fill it,
if it is not there then there is a form
Form 60,
so I will give you the
link of Form 60 also in the description, you can
download it from there and fill it because
it will be accepted only if someone does not have a PAN card, if there is no PAN card
then this Form 60 will not be accepted,
so
you have to
attach one of the original bank's cancelled cheques, which is your
cheque, after cancelling it like this you have to attach that,
you have to attach the main two things,
one you have to attach that and one PAN,
if you do not have PAN then you have to attach a copy of
which I told you about Form 60, you have to attach a
copy of Form 60, after that sign here
Whose place will it be, it will be
Mukesh's here only and how will it be, as per the PAN
card, like it will be on the PAN card, so
if there is no PAN card, then like he will
fill Form 60, you have to do it accordingly
and the way you will sign on Form 60,
you have to sign here exactly in the same way
and you have to sign here also.
Here it will be of the owner only, the
signature will be of the owner only.  Otherwise it cannot belong to anyone.
So today we have filled the complete claim form of
ICICI LB.  I have told you
what are the differences between cashless and non-cashless policies.  How many
types of policies are there?  I have told you this
and I will make a video on Form
60.  As soon as possible
I will make a video of Form 60 and will
fill it and show you how Form 60
is filled and will make a video of
how its process happens that you have to go to the company
and what all you need and along with it whatever
documents you need, you
need Aadhar, Aadhar
PAN,
RC,
insurance
and driving license, whichever one is driving,
DL which we call copy of insurance, all these
need photostat,
photostat, okay, all these need photostat, which we
call Xerox, of which we need black
and white photo, we need all these,
these are all your documents.  So if
anyone has any doubt then he can
ask me by commenting.  I will
tell him how it happens.  He
can ask me by commenting if he has any
doubts left.  If someone is
not able to fill his claim form and it is
not getting filled by the company then he can get his claim registered with me for
just a small amount of ₹100, right here in the
office itself,
so you will have to pay
me ₹100
and I will get your claim registered from here, will
tell you everything and you
just have to go and I will tell you about the company also.
Where do you want to park your car?  After going there,
you just have to go and park there
and when your car is ready,
you have to go and receive it.  Just
if you pay me this ₹100,
I will register your claim from here.  I will
tell you where you have to go
and what documents will be required for it. The documents that I have mentioned,
you should keep the normal charges that the
photostat guy should take it, then only ₹50,
which will be my hard work, which will be the hard work of this company,
we will keep that, so
if anyone has any doubt about this, he
can ask me by commenting and you can tell me
which insurance do you have
?  Please send me his photo.  If you want, you can
tell me in the comments
which company you have, then I will
fill its claim form and tell you
how to fill it.  So
if anyone has any doubt regarding its entire process, he
can ask me in the comment and subscribe to this channel from here
and share this with every two wheeler and four wheeler
owner who has vehicles
and
also like it.  If you have any doubt,
you can ask me in the comments
and if anyone wants to get this done, he
can also tell me in the comments, then I will
contact him myself and thank you for
liking, sharing and subscribing to my video,
thanks chal